

Developer with 4 years of experience in web environment and 4 years of experience as a teacher. I completed several successful web projects providing full-fledged support to customers, as well as developing functional and friendly web interfaces for users. Experience in marketplace commercial development with a team of professionals involving up-todate IT technologies. Being highly proficient, I was entrusted to develop a separate web application individually within the project. High skills of communication and cooperation. Active team player. Interested in self-development and selfimprovement. Highly responsible and diligent.

CONTACT DETAILS

) +380933584871

) +380974343441



DMYTRO LOBODIN

EXPERIENCE

Junior Front-End Developer Salad LLC

2021-2022

- Fully-fledged website development for marketplace using NEXT.JS,
- Work with API and REST requests, Google Maps, Open Street Map,
- Component model development,
- Work with user interface, authentication,
- Individual project of product collector web app development using React Framework.

Freelance WEB Developer

2018-nowadays

- Development, optimization, promotion of web projects,
- Creation of websites from scratch on a turnkey basis,
- Programming of functional features for web environment.

Projects:

- Legend Restaurant: http://restaurant-legend.com.ua/
- WinProfi distributor: http://winprofi.com.ua/
- Wedding invitation: https://jonasliubov.github.io/

Teacher

STEP Computer Academy

2016-2020; 2022-nowadays

Teacher at Software Development and Programming Department majoring in:

- Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C/C++,
- Mobile developments,
- Unity game development.

EDUCATION

STEP Computer Academy

2013-2016

Completed course in Software Development and Programming.

KEY SKILLS

- Proficient: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Git
- Basic: C++, C, Python, Java, C#, Unity, PHP, Three.is, Next.is, Node.is, Laravel, Django
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, jQuery, JSON, React, NEXT.JS, Redux, Firebase, GoogleMaps, OpenStreetMap
- Development of compression algorithms